{
    "questions": [
        {
            "id": 1,
            "question": "Who kills Sirius Black during the battle at the Ministry of Magic?",
            "correctAnswer": "Bellatrix Lestrange",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Remus Lupin",
                "Lord Voldemort",
                "Fenrir Greyback"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "question": "Which Hogwarts student is harmed by a cursed necklace?",
            "correctAnswer": "Katie Bell",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Lavender Brown",
                "Draco Malfoy",
                "Cedric Diggory"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 3,
            "question": "What spell does Hermione use to stop the rogue Bludged that targets Harry during a Quidditch match against Slytherin?",
            "correctAnswer": "Finite Incantatem",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Badgering",
                "Depulso",
                "Bombarda"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 4,
            "question": "What present does Sirius leave Harry in his third year?",
            "correctAnswer": "A firebolt broomstick",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "A Nimbus 2000 broomstick",
                "A Nimbus 2001 broomstick",
                "A Comet 290 broomstick"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 5,
            "question": "What is the name of the landlord of the Leaky Cauldron?",
            "correctAnswer": "Tom",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Henry",
                "Hagrid",
                "Rufus"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 6,
            "question": "Who does Harry hear singing when he opens the golden egg under water?",
            "correctAnswer": "Merpeople",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Veela",
                "Phoenix",
                "Goblins"
            ]
        }
        ,
        {
            "id": 7,
            "question": "What does Dumbledore conjure to protect himself and Harry from the Inferi in the cave?",
            "correctAnswer": "Fire",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Water",
                "Air",
                "Earth"
            ]
        }
        ,
        {
            "id": 8,
            "question": "Which Triwizard Tournament cahmpion abandons the second task without completing it?",
            "correctAnswer": "Fleur Delacour",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Harry Potter",
                "Cedric Diggory",
                "Viktor Krum"
            ]
        }
        ,
        {
            "id": 9,
            "question": "What are the effects of the spell Fera Verto as taught by Professor McGiagall to her students in their second year?",
            "correctAnswer": "Turns animals into water goblets",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Makes things disappear",
                "Turns matches into needles",
                "Makes things appear from thin air"
            ]
        }
        ,
        {
            "id": 10,
            "question": "What phrase appears on the Golden Snitch after Harry presses it agaist his lips?",
            "correctAnswer": "I open at the close",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "I open when time is right",
                "I open under water",
                "I open when you need it the most"
            ]
        }
        ,
        {
            "id": 11,
            "question": "Who was Katie Bell convinced she had to deliver the cursed necklace to?",
            "correctAnswer": "Professor Dumbledore",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Professor Snape",
                "Professor McGonagall",
                "Professor Sprout"
            ]
        }
        ,
        {
            "id": 12,
            "question": "What kind of creature attacks Hermione in the girl's toilets?",
            "correctAnswer": "A troll",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "A gigant",
                "A vampire",
                "A ghost"
            ]
        }
        ,
        {
            "id": 13,
            "question": "Who kills Bellatrix Lestrange after the battle of Hogwarts?",
            "correctAnswer": "Molly Weasley",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Harry Potter",
                "Neville Longbottom",
                "Severus Snape"
            ]
        }
        ,
        {
            "id": 14,
            "question": "After Harry has taken Felix Felicis what does he catch Professor Slughorn doing?",
            "correctAnswer": "Cutting Venomous Tentacula leaves",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Stealing potion ingredients from Professor Snapes secret stash",
                "Taking venomous Acromantula poison from Aragog",
                "Drinking whiskey at his office"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 15,
            "question": "Who does Tonks marry?",
            "correctAnswer": "Remus Lupin",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Bill Weasley",
                "Charlie Weasley",
                "Sirius Black"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 16,
            "question": "What spell does Hermione use to freeze the Cornish pixies after they wreak havoc in Professor Lockhart's classroom?",
            "correctAnswer": "Immobilus",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Petrificus Totalus",
                "Expelliarmus",
                "Rictusempra"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 17,
            "question": "What do Harry and Hermione use to travel back in time?",
            "correctAnswer": "A Time-Turner",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "A Portkey",
                "A Vanishing Cabinet",
                "A magical mirror"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 18,
            "question": "What position does Oliver Wood play for the Gryffindor Quidditch Team?",
            "correctAnswer": "Keeper",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Seeker",
                "Chaser",
                "Beater"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 19,
            "question": "What form does the Patronus take that leads Harry to the lake where he finds the sword of Gryffindor?",
            "correctAnswer": "A doe",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "A stag",
                "A wolf",
                "An otter"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 20,
            "question": "Who signs a note left inside the fake locket Horcrux?",
            "correctAnswer": "Regulus Arcturus Black",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Sirius Black",
                "Albus Dumbledore",
                "Severus Snape"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 21,
            "question": "What does Madam Hooch teach at Hogwarts?",
            "correctAnswer": "Flying lessons",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Herbology",
                "Transfiguration",
                "Potions"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 22,
            "question": "Why does Hermione use the spell Protego Totalum around the trio's campsite after they escape the Ministry of Magic?",
            "correctAnswer": "It's a protective enchantment",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "To repel animals",
                "To make them invisible",
                "To silence their voices"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 23,
            "question": "How many turns does Dumbledore suggest Hermione give the Time-Turner to go back and save Sirius?",
            "correctAnswer": "Three",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Two",
                "Five",
                "Four"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 24,
            "question": "According to Aunt Muriel, what serious crime did Professor Dumbledore's father commit?",
            "correctAnswer": "He killed three Muggles",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "He attacked a wizard",
                "He robbed Gringotts",
                "He cast an Unforgivable Curse"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 25,
            "question": "What is the name of Hagrid's half-brother?",
            "correctAnswer": "Grawp",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Fang",
                "Aragog",
                "Norbert"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 26,
            "question": "What does Ron drink in Professor Slughorn's office that has been poisoned?",
            "correctAnswer": "Mead",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Butterbeer",
                "Pumpkin juice",
                "Firewhisky"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 27,
            "question": "Which ghost appears at the first start-of-term feast with a sword in his hand?",
            "correctAnswer": "The Bloody Baron",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Nearly Headless Nick",
                "The Grey Lady",
                "Peeves"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 28,
            "question": "What is the effect of the Incendio spell?",
            "correctAnswer": "It creates fire",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "It freezes objects",
                "It creates a shield",
                "It summons objects"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 29,
            "question": "What does Professor Lupin give Harry to eat after the Dementors attack them?",
            "correctAnswer": "Chocolate",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Butterbeer",
                "Pumpkin Pasties",
                "Treacle Tart"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 30,
            "question": "Where are Dudley and Harry when the Dementors attack them?",
            "correctAnswer": "In an underpass",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "In a park",
                "On Privet Drive",
                "At a train station"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 31,
            "question": "Who kills Professor Dumbledore?",
            "correctAnswer": "Severus Snape",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Bellatrix Lestrange",
                "Fenrir Greyback",
                "Draco Malfoy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 32,
            "question": "What time does the Hogwarts Express leave King's Cross Station on the first day of term?",
            "correctAnswer": "11:00 am",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "10:30 am",
                "12:00 pm",
                "9:45 am"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 33,
            "question": "Which spell produces light from the end of the wand?",
            "correctAnswer": "Lumos",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Nox",
                "Incendio",
                "Alohomora"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 34,
            "question": "What does Ron see when he looks into the Mirror of Erised?",
            "correctAnswer": "He is Head Boy and is also holding the Quidditch Cup as Quidditch captain",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Himself with Hermione",
                "Himself as Minister of Magic",
                "Himself with the Elder Wand"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 35,
            "question": "Who is the headmistress of Beauxbatons Academy of Magic?",
            "correctAnswer": "Madame Maxime",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Professor Sprout",
                "Madame Pomfrey",
                "Madam Rosmerta"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 36,
            "question": "What is the name of the Black family house-elf?",
            "correctAnswer": "Kreacher",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Dobby",
                "Winky",
                "Hokey"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 37,
            "question": "What does the Dark Mark look like?",
            "correctAnswer": "A skull with a serpent coming out of its mouth",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "A snake in a triangle",
                "A lightning bolt",
                "A dragon symbol"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 38,
            "question": "What phrase is etched into Harry's hand during his detention with Professor Umbridge?",
            "correctAnswer": "I must not tell lies",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "I am a rule-breaker",
                "I will respect authority",
                "I will follow the rules"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 39,
            "question": "What book does Hermione take from the library to make Polyjuice Potion?",
            "correctAnswer": "Moste Potente Potions",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Advanced Potion-Making",
                "Magical Drafts and Potions",
                "Secrets of Dark Arts"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 40,
            "question": "The core of Harry Potter's wand is made from what?",
            "correctAnswer": "Tail feather of a phoenix",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Unicorn hair",
                "Dragon heartstring",
                "Acromantula hair"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 41,
            "question": "When Professor Trelawney predicts 'servant and master shall be reunited once more,' she is referring to which servant?",
            "correctAnswer": "Peter Pettigrew",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Bellatrix Lestrange",
                "Barty Crouch Jr.",
                "Lucius Malfoy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 42,
            "question": "What creature does Mad-Eye Moody use to teach the Unforgivable Curses?",
            "correctAnswer": "A spider",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "A snake",
                "A frog",
                "A rat"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 43,
            "question": "Who does Voldemort order to kill Snape?",
            "correctAnswer": "Nagini",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Bellatrix Lestrange",
                "Fenrir Greyback",
                "Lucius Malfoy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 44,
            "question": "Which teacher starts the Dueling Club at Hogwarts during Harry's second year?",
            "correctAnswer": "Professor Lockhart",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Professor Snape",
                "Professor Flitwick",
                "Professor McGonagall"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 45,
            "question": "According to Ron, what happens to a wizard or witch if they break an Unbreakable Vow?",
            "correctAnswer": "They die",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "They lose their magic",
                "They become a Squib",
                "They are exiled"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 46,
            "question": "What object does Hagrid conceal the broken part of his wand in?",
            "correctAnswer": "Pink umbrella",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Walking stick",
                "Large book",
                "Boot"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 47,
            "question": "Who is the author of The Life and Lies of Albus Dumbledore?",
            "correctAnswer": "Rita Skeeter",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Bathilda Bagshot",
                "Xenophilius Lovegood",
                "Gilderoy Lockhart"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 48,
            "question": "What is Sirius' nickname when disguised as a dog?",
            "correctAnswer": "Padfoot",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Moony",
                "Prongs",
                "Snuffles"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 49,
            "question": "Who cast the Dark Mark into the sky once Dumbledore has been killed?",
            "correctAnswer": "Bellatrix Lestrange",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Severus Snape",
                "Lucius Malfoy",
                "Fenrir Greyback"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 50,
            "question": "Which student is approached by the snake that Draco Malfoy conjures during the Dueling Club?",
            "correctAnswer": "Justin Finch-Fletchley",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Seamus Finnigan",
                "Dean Thomas",
                "Colin Creevey"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 51,
            "question": "What does the spell Morsmordre produce?",
            "correctAnswer": "It fires the Dark Mark into the sky",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "It summons Death Eaters",
                "It creates a shield",
                "It produces a black mist"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 52,
            "question": "What means of transportation do Harry and Hagrid use during their escape from Privet Drive?",
            "correctAnswer": "A flying motorbike",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "A Thestral carriage",
                "A broomstick",
                "A portkey"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 53,
            "question": "What is Mad-Eye Moody's first name?",
            "correctAnswer": "Alastor",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Bartemius",
                "Gideon",
                "Mundungus"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 54,
            "question": "According to Luna, what is a Wrackspurt?",
            "correctAnswer": "An invisible creature that floats into your ears and makes your brain go fuzzy",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "A creature that lives in shadows",
                "A spirit that causes headaches",
                "A charm that wards off Dementors"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 55,
            "question": "What is the name of the orphanage where Professor Dumbledore finds Tom Riddle?",
            "correctAnswer": "Wool's Orphanage",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Riddle House",
                "Little Hangleton Home",
                "Yorkshire Shelter"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 56,
            "question": "What subject does Professor Sprout teach at Hogwarts?",
            "correctAnswer": "Herbology",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Potions",
                "Transfiguration",
                "Care of Magical Creatures"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 57,
            "question": "Who uses the Petrificus Totalus spell on Neville to immobilize him and leave the Gryffindor Tower?",
            "correctAnswer": "Hermione Granger",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Harry Potter",
                "Ron Weasley",
                "Draco Malfoy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 58,
            "question": "What are the initials on the note from the fake Horcrux?",
            "correctAnswer": "R.A.B",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "S.S.",
                "L.M.",
                "A.D."
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 59,
            "question": "Who has the first name Dolores?",
            "correctAnswer": "Professor Umbridge",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Professor Trelawney",
                "Bellatrix Lestrange",
                "Aunt Petunia"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 60,
            "question": "What musical instrument do Harry, Ron, and Hermione find playing near Fluffy?",
            "correctAnswer": "A Harp",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "A flute",
                "A piano",
                "A lyre"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 61,
            "question": "Who destroys the final Horcrux?",
            "correctAnswer": "Neville Longbottom",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Harry Potter",
                "Ron Weasley",
                "Hermione Granger"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 62,
            "question": "What is the name of the group of students organized by Professor Umbridge to help her police Hogwarts?",
            "correctAnswer": "The Inquisitorial Squad",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "The Hogwarts Guard",
                "The Prefects",
                "The Defense Committee"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 63,
            "question": "What potion does Harry take to help him extract the memory he needs from Slughorn?",
            "correctAnswer": "Felix Felicis",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Polyjuice Potion",
                "Veritaserum",
                "Amortentia"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 64,
            "question": "Who is the first champion to be chosen by the Goblet of Fire?",
            "correctAnswer": "Viktor Krum",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Cedric Diggory",
                "Fleur Delacour",
                "Harry Potter"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 65,
            "question": "Who is Remus Lupin's wife?",
            "correctAnswer": "Nymphadora Tonks",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Lily Potter",
                "Molly Weasley",
                "Bellatrix Lestrange"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 66,
            "question": "What is the name of Neville's toad?",
            "correctAnswer": "Trevor",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Binky",
                "Fang",
                "Scabbers"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 67,
            "question": "Which Death Eaters find Harry, Ron, and Hermione in the café in London after they escape from Bill and Fleur's wedding?",
            "correctAnswer": "Rowle and Dolohov",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Crabbe and Goyle",
                "Yaxley and Bellatrix",
                "Avery and Mulciber"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 68,
            "question": "In which school book does Hermione read that the ceiling of the Great Hall is bewitched to look like the night sky?",
            "correctAnswer": "Hogwarts: A History",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "The Standard Book of Spells",
                "Magical Theory",
                "Fantastic Beasts and Where to Find Them"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 69,
            "question": "Which spell does Luna use to fix Harry's broken nose?",
            "correctAnswer": "Episkey",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Reparo",
                "Ferula",
                "Orchideous"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 70,
            "question": "Where is the Pensieve located?",
            "correctAnswer": "Dumbledore's office",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "The Room of Requirement",
                "The Defense Against the Dark Arts classroom",
                "The Astronomy Tower"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 71,
            "question": "What are the names of Neville Longbottom's parents?",
            "correctAnswer": "Frank and Alice",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "James and Lily",
                "Ted and Andromeda",
                "Molly and Arthur"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 72,
            "question": "Which creatures work in Gringotts bank?",
            "correctAnswer": "Goblins",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "House-elves",
                "House-ghosts",
                "Centaurs"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 73,
            "question": "Who is the thief that Harry sees, through Voldemort's mind, jumping out of a window of Gregorovitch's wand shop?",
            "correctAnswer": "Gellert Grindelwald",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Sirius Black",
                "Fenrir Greyback",
                "Peter Pettigrew"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 74,
            "question": "How do first-year students travel from Hogsmeade station to Hogwarts castle?",
            "correctAnswer": "By boat",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "By Thestral carriage",
                "By broomstick",
                "By flying carpet"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 75,
            "question": "Who helps Ron during his Quidditch tryout by discreetly casting a Confundus Charm on Cormac McLaggen?",
            "correctAnswer": "Hermione Granger",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Ginny Weasley",
                "Luna Lovegood",
                "Neville Longbottom"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 76,
            "question": "What is at the core of Lucius Malfoy's wand?",
            "correctAnswer": "Dragon heartstring",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Unicorn hair",
                "Phoenix feather",
                "Veela hair"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 77,
            "question": "What is Umbridge's position at the Ministry of Magic when Harry is tried for using underage magic?",
            "correctAnswer": "Senior Undersecretary to the Minister",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Head of Magical Law Enforcement",
                "Auror in Chief",
                "Head of the Department of Mysteries"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 78,
            "question": "Who, under the effects of the Imperius Curse, leads Harry, Ron, Hermione, and Griphook to Bellatrix Lestrange's vault?",
            "correctAnswer": "Bogrod the goblin",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Griphook the goblin",
                "Ragnok the goblin",
                "Dobby the house-elf"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 79,
            "question": "Before the battle of Hogwarts, whose voice is heard speaking to the students and teachers in the Great Hall?",
            "correctAnswer": "Lord Voldemort",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Professor Snape",
                "Bellatrix Lestrange",
                "Lucius Malfoy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 80,
            "question": "The students from Beauxbatons Academy arrive at Hogwarts flying in a carriage pulled by what?",
            "correctAnswer": "Flying horses",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Dragons",
                "Thestrals",
                "Griffins"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 81,
            "question": "What does Hermione add to the Polyjuice Potion in order to transform into Bellatrix Lestrange?",
            "correctAnswer": "A strand of Bellatrix's hair",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Bellatrix's wand",
                "A drop of her blood",
                "Her Dark Mark imprint"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 82,
            "question": "Which story from The Tales of Beedle the Bard tells of the Deathly Hallows?",
            "correctAnswer": "The Tale of the Three Brothers",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "The Fountain of Fair Fortune",
                "The Warlock's Hairy Heart",
                "Babbitty Rabbitty and Her Cackling Stump"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 83,
            "question": "What does Professor Slughorn call Ron in the Three Broomsticks after inviting Harry and Hermione to join him for his supper club?",
            "correctAnswer": "Wallenby",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Weasley",
                "Redman",
                "Rudderman"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 84,
            "question": "What is the name of the Gringotts goblin who takes Harry to his vault for the first time?",
            "correctAnswer": "Griphook",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Bogrod",
                "Ragnok",
                "Kreacher"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 85,
            "question": "Who is taken captive when Harry goes to face Voldemort in the Forbidden Forest after the battle of Hogwarts?",
            "correctAnswer": "Hagrid",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Luna Lovegood",
                "Professor McGonagall",
                "Neville Longbottom"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 86,
            "question": "Who does Harry invite to Slughorn's Christmas party?",
            "correctAnswer": "Luna Lovegood",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Ginny Weasley",
                "Hermione Granger",
                "Cho Chang"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 87,
            "question": "What type of memory is needed for a Patronus Charm to work?",
            "correctAnswer": "A happy and powerful memory",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "A fearful memory",
                "An exciting memory",
                "A neutral memory"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 88,
            "question": "On their quest for the Philosopher's Stone, Harry, Ron, and Hermione need to catch what flying object?",
            "correctAnswer": "A key",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "A broomstick",
                "A wand",
                "A golden snitch"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 89,
            "question": "Who is speculated to be the informant leaking Dumbledore's secrets in Rita Skeeter's book?",
            "correctAnswer": "Bathilda Bagshot",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Elphias Doge",
                "Aberforth Dumbledore",
                "Gellert Grindelwald"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 90,
            "question": "What does Fawkes do the first time Harry meets him in Dumbledore's office?",
            "correctAnswer": "Bursts into flames",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Sings a magical song",
                "Flies around the room",
                "Sheds a feather"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 91,
            "question": "How does Harry Potter destroy Tom Riddle's diary?",
            "correctAnswer": "With a Basilisk fang",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "With a spell",
                "By burning it",
                "With the sword of Gryffindor"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 92,
            "question": "Which Ravenclaw schoolmate from Hogwarts do Harry and Ron find imprisoned in the dungeons of Malfoy Manor?",
            "correctAnswer": "Luna Lovegood",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Cho Chang",
                "Padma Patil",
                "Michael Corner"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 93,
            "question": "What is the name for the most powerful love potion in the world that Professor Slughorn introduces the class to in his first lesson?",
            "correctAnswer": "Amortentia",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Felix Felicis",
                "Veritaserum",
                "Polyjuice Potion"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 94,
            "question": "Who became the master of the Elder Wand after Gellert Grindelwald?",
            "correctAnswer": "Albus Dumbledore",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Lord Voldemort",
                "Severus Snape",
                "Harry Potter"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 95,
            "question": "How many times has Gilderoy Lockhart won Witch Weekly's Most-Charming-Smile Award?",
            "correctAnswer": "Five times",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Three times",
                "Seven times",
                "Nine times"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 96,
            "question": "What does Madame Maxime tell Hagrid that her horses drink?",
            "correctAnswer": "Single-malt whiskey",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Pumpkin juice",
                "Butterbeer",
                "Dragon's milk"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 97,
            "question": "Who is asked to identify Harry at Malfoy Manor when the Snatchers catch him?",
            "correctAnswer": "Draco Malfoy",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Lucius Malfoy",
                "Bellatrix Lestrange",
                "Fenrir Greyback"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 98,
            "question": "What subject does Professor Trelawney teach?",
            "correctAnswer": "Divination",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Astronomy",
                "Herbology",
                "Charms"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 99,
            "question": "Who casts Fiendfyre in the Room of Requirement?",
            "correctAnswer": "Gregory Goyle",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Draco Malfoy",
                "Vincent Crabbe",
                "Blaise Zabini"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 100,
            "question": "Whose wizard card does Harry find in his Chocolate Frog the first time he opens one?",
            "correctAnswer": "Albus Dumbledore",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Godric Gryffindor",
                "Salazar Slytherin",
                "Merlin"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 101,
            "question": "Who does Harry, as Albert Runcorn, and Hermione, as Mafalda Hopkirk, run into in an elevator at the Ministry of Magic?",
            "correctAnswer": "Dolores Umbridge",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Arthur Weasley",
                "Percy Weasley",
                "Lucius Malfoy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 102,
            "question": "How does Harry kill the Basilisk in the Chamber of Secrets?",
            "correctAnswer": "With the sword of Gryffindor",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "With a spell",
                "With a rock",
                "With a potion"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 103,
            "question": "How do you split your soul to create a Horcrux?",
            "correctAnswer": "By killing someone",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "By casting a spell",
                "By drinking a potion",
                "By making a sacrifice"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 104,
            "question": "How do Harry and Ron finally get to Hogwarts for their second year?",
            "correctAnswer": "By a flying car",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "By broomstick",
                "By Thestral",
                "By the Hogwarts Express"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 105,
            "question": "What color are the streams of light emitted from a wand when it performs the Killing Curse?",
            "correctAnswer": "Green",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Red",
                "Blue",
                "Purple"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 106,
            "question": "What does Harry discover about the locket that he and Professor Dumbledore retrieve from the basin in the cave?",
            "correctAnswer": "That it is fake",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "That it is a cursed item",
                "That it belongs to Bellatrix",
                "That it cannot be destroyed"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 107,
            "question": "What is the name of the Ministry of Magic employee that Ron impersonates using Polyjuice Potion?",
            "correctAnswer": "Reg Cattermole",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "Albert Runcorn",
                "Mundungus Fletcher",
                "Percival Pratt"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 108,
            "question": "What type of creature saves Harry from Voldemort in the Forbidden Forest?",
            "correctAnswer": "A centaur",
            "wrongAnswers": [
                "A unicorn",
                "A phoenix",
                "A Thestral"
            ]
        }
    ]
}